{
    "easyQuestions": 
    [
        {
            "questionText": "When Was The First Doom Released?",
            "answers": [
                "1993", "1996", "1991", "1995"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "1993"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What Is The Name Of The Protagonist Of Doom?",
            "answers": [
                "DoomGuy", "Hector Braveheart", "Doom Master", "Sargent Maelstrom"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "DoomGuy"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What Genre Is Doom Often Crediting With Pioneering?",
            "answers": [
                "Horror", "The First Person Shooter", "Puzzle Game", "Action RPG"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The First Person Shooter"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "In The First Doom Game, Doomguy is Left Guarding The Perimeter Of The Phobos Facility Armed With What Weapon?",
            "answers": [
                "A Chainsaw", "An Assault Rifle", "A BFG", "A Pistol"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "A Pistol"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "Which Difficulty Was Added As A Joke?",
            "answers": [
                "Fairy Tale Difficulty", "Nightmare", "Ultra-Violence", "Super Easy"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Nightmare"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What Is Doomguy's Catchphrase?",
            "answers": [
                "He Never Talks", "'Rip And Tear!'", "'War... War Never Changes'", "'Get Ready To Die'"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "He Never Talks"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "Why Did Bosses Famously Hate Doom (1993)?",
            "answers": [
                "Because Old People Didn't Know How To Play It", "It Apparently Reduced Worker's Productivity", "Because It Had Hidden Messages Denigrating Corporations", "They Wanted To Play But Everyone Kept It Secret"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "It Apparently Reduced Worker's Productivity"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What Weapon, Other Than Fists, Is Used For Close Combat?",
            "answers": [
                "Chainsaw", "Light Saber", "Cyber Axe", "Power Hammer"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Chainsaw"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "Why Was Doom Mentioned In A 1993 Congressional Hearing?",
            "answers": [
                "An Example Of Hardworking Americans", "Extreme Violence", "Because Doom Clones Were Violating Copyright Laws", "Because Doom Was used by Osama Bin Laden"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Extreme Violence"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What Military Group Is Doomguy Part Of?",
            "answers": [
                "Space Marines", "UAC Security", "The Space Rangers", "The United States Demon Response Force"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Space Marines"
        }
    ],
    "hardQuestions": 
    [
        {
            "questionText": "What Is The Software Company Associated With Doom?",
            "answers": [
                "Ubisoft", "Interplay", "Bungie", "id Software"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "id Software"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "The Original Doom Had Such A Huge Impact On The FPS Genre, That For A While All FPS Games Were Known As...?",
            "answers": [
                "Doomers", "Doom Games", "Doom Sequels", "Doom Clones"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Doom Clones"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "Why Was Doomguy First Sent To Mars?",
            "answers": [
                "He Was There On Holiday", "It Was A Punishment For Assaulting A Superior Officer", "They Knew That Only He Could Stop The Demons", "He Was On A Mission To Quell A Civil War Among The Mars Colonists"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "It Was A Punishment For Assaulting A Superior Officer"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What Does The 'UAC' Stand For?",
            "answers": [
                "Union Aerospace Corporation", "United Arab Commandos", "Unharnessing Argent Coduits", "United Adventure Corporation"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Union Aerospace Corporation"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What First Caused The Opening Of A Portal To Hell?",
            "answers": [
                "They Drilled Too Far Into Mars", "Someone Messed With A Ouija Board", "Experimentation On Genetics", "Experimentation On Teleportation"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Experimentation On Teleportation"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "Who Is The Final Boss In Doom 1?",
            "answers": [
                "Cyberdemon", "Harlot Of Hell", "Satan", "Muscle Demon"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Cyberdemon"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "Who Is The Final Boss In Doom 2?",
            "answers": [
                "Beezlebub", "Icon Of Sin", "Goat Whore", "Lucifer"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Icon Of Sin"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What Does BFG Stand For?",
            "answers": [
                "Barium-Fulcrum Gun", "Big F**king Gun", "Ballistic Fluorescence Gun", "Big Friendly Giant"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Big F**king Gun"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What Powerup In The New Doom Game Allows You To Beat Demons To Death With Your Bare Hands?",
            "answers": [
                "Quad Damage", "Berserk", "Invulnerability", "Mayhem"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Berserk"
        }
        ,
        {
            "questionText": "What Is The Final Boss In The Newest Doom Game?",
            "answers": [
                "Sauron", "Cyberdemon", "Hell Knights", "Spider Mastermind"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Spider Mastermind"
        }
    ]
}